Sir tell me, I will give you two stocks of the day, Deep. Today the
first one is buy and one is sell. The first one is
ICICI Lombard. Here I am
giving the level of 1633 futures.
1633 is your stop loss level.
For the target of 1680 and 1695, the results have
come yesterday. The results are very good.
Much better than expected. I did
not expect such good numbers on every parameter.
Secondly, there is a report from Jefferies with a target of 1950. This is
already
maintained. Even though Silas has downgraded, it has
increased the target with it. It has
not reduced the target. HSBC has a
target of 1990. I think if
you look at the numbers in terms of net premium one also, it is
better than expected. The profit has come better. The
numbers are good on every parameter. You should
like this stock. The second stock is a
sell opinion. I want to sell. We are positive on Tata
Communications futures in the long term.
You know,
but from the short term perspective, there is only
one option in this company.  The problem is there is
no stability in the results. One or two
quarters are good, then they turn bad,
then they rise, then they turn bad again. I think
you had highlighted the last quarter as well,
Kans, at least show good results for four quarters, I
mean, yes, you have given us some
confidence from somewhere, right? There is confidence, the
company is Tata, the
work done in digital is amazing, no
one has any doubt about it, but there is
no consistency in the results. Today we will
also interview the management, then we will know and understand from
them why this is happening, right? Till then, the
opinion is to sell for now, because the stock had run up a
bit in the last few days
before the results, I think it can be gutted. The
stop loss is 1915. The target is 1860, 1848
and 1838. You have to sell for these three targets. The
results are showing a little weaker than expected.
Operational performance has been weak on every parameter.
Their margin has
decreased from 20 to 185. This is a
bit of a margin reduction, if not a good sign, then I think the
stock may become a little weak once and can be sold.
This advice is not for long term investors, they should keep it
in their portfolio,
this is for short term traders and at 9:00
I have a stock which is different from the results and
is also on the basis of news and bring the stock in which
some good action can happen, it is
on the long side, okay let's go and